<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existed mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
	<ModId Value="124159" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="Magic Garbage + Trash Boss" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
	<ShortDescription Value="Auto-Clean garbage OR use Trash Boss = Self manage trucks + facilities" />
	<!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<!--LongDescription Value="This is a long description" /-->
	<LongDescription>
**Magic Garbage + Trash Boss**

Two ways to handle garbage, a Status Report option, and all new POWER Users section for experiments.
---

### OPTION 1  AUTO CLEAN
- ✅ **Total Magic On**
- Removes all garbage automatically.
- Garbage warning icons cleared
- Trucks and facilities become mostly cosmetic.
- Mod does not stop Garbage system; cleanup is just very fast.

### OPTION 2  SELF MANAGE
- ✅ **Trash Boss On**
- Keep vanilla garbage gameplay, and allows adjustable garbage values.
- Adjust garbage trucks, facilities, other factors to reduce traffic and service strain.
- 🚚 Great for players who still want to see trucks driving around, with fewer problems.

**Threshold slider**
- Advanced option (mod worked fine before this slider; it's bonus for power users)
- Increase means garbage levels can be much higher before the building calls for a truck (reduce truck dispatches). May need higher truck capacity.
Balance advised: use status log button to check details while tweaking this. Allow city to run a few hours between threshold changes to get better analysis.

**Helper buttons**
- [Game Defaults] = reset all sliders to 100% (pure vanilla).
- [Recommended]	  = suggested preset values for easy management.
- Standard Trash Boss buttons do not change Power User section.

### NEW STATUS Report
- Real garbage stats help a Trash Boss figure out what is happening.
- Lean: status does not run in-city per frame; runs in Options menu for best performance to not affect gameplay.


### NEW OPTIONAL POWER USER
- Not needed for most players; allows advanced tuning and experimentation.
- Most cities get good results just using the Trash Boss Options and not touching Power User settings.
- Extra controls:
- Dispatch Request Threshold + Pickup Threshold
- **Pickup** cannot be higher than **Dispatch Request**.
- Garbage Happiness Baseline + Garbage Happiness Step
- Garbage Accumulation Rate (not needed for most cities, this is a powerful adjustment, use with caution)
- Higher thresholds can reduce truck traffic, but too high can slow pickups too much.

#### Support and feedback
- If the mod helps you, give it a Like, it's free + easy :)
- Feedback on: Github, Discord, etc., links on this page.

---

### Compatibility
- Works with new and existing cities. Safe to remove any time.
- Does not use Harmony patch, lightweight; anything with sliders is done in options menu, not in-game, for best performance.

---

### Credits
- RiverMochi - author
- Thanks to Wayz for inspiration on the original Magical Garbage mod
- yenyang - code review, tech advice
- Necko1996 - testing, screenshots
- gagaxm - truck image

#### 11 languages
- English, Français French, Deutsch German, Español Spanish, Italiano Italian
- 日本語 Japanese, 한국어 Korean, Português Brasil, Polski Polish
- 简体中文 Simplified Chinese, 繁體中文 Traditional Chinese

</LongDescription>
	<!--Thumbnail-->
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/thumbnail-garbageTruck.jpg" />
	<!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
    <Screenshot Value="Properties/10-image-TotalMagic.jpg" />
    <Screenshot Value="Properties/30-image-TrashBoss.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/40-image-Status.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/60-image-UsageEN.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/70-image-Before.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/80-image-After.jpg" />
	<!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
	<Tag Value="Code Mod" />
	<!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
	<ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/magic-garbage-truck.1867844/" />
	<!--Version of the mod-->
	<ModVersion Value="1.2.7" />
	<!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
	<GameVersion Value="1.5.*" />
	<!--Dependency for the mod, can be set multiple times-->
	<Dependency Id="" />
	<!--Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
<ChangeLog>
* added optional Power User advanced settings for garbage tuning
* added Garbage Accumulation Rate for power users to tinker with; not needed for most cities.
* added optional Building threshold slider; triggers when a truck is dispatched
* added more detailed Status log info to mod Options menu.
* updated all locale files.

</ChangeLog>
<!--External link. supported types are discord, github, youtube, twitch, x, paypal, patreon-->
<ExternalLink Type="discord" Url="https://discord.gg/HTav7ARPs2" />
<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/River-Mochi/MagicGarbage" />

</Publish>
